export default [
    {
        question: "0",
        answer: "z√©ro"
    },
    {
        question: "1",
        answer: "un",
        highlight: "I talks",
    },
    {
        question: "2",
        answer: "deux",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "3",
        answer: "trois",
        highlight: "She talks",
    },
    {
        question: "4",
        answer: "quatre",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "5",
        answer: "cinq",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "6",
        answer: "six",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "7",
        answer: "sept",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "8",
        answer: "huit",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "9",
        answer: "neuf",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "10",
        answer: "dix",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "11",
        answer: "onze",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "12",
        answer: "douze",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "13",
        answer: "treize",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "14",
        answer: "quatorze",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "15",
        answer: "quinze",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "16",
        answer: "seize",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "20",
        answer: "vingt",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "30",
        answer: "trentre",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "40",
        answer: "quarante",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "50",
        answer: "cinquante",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "60",
        answer: "soixante",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "70",
        answer: "soixante dix",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "80",
        answer: "quatre vingts",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "90",
        answer: "quatre vingts dix",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "100",
        answer: "cent",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "1,000",
        answer: "mille",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "1,000,000",
        answer: "un million",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "200",
        answer: "deux cents",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "2020",
        answer: "deux mille vingt",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "1998",
        answer: "mille neuf cent quatre vingt dix huit",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
    {
        question: "15,000",
        answer: "quinze mille",
        highlight: "You talks",
    },
]